[{"answer": " my friend? What's wrong? What's happened", "docId": "Martha-Marcy-May-Marlene.txt", "asentId": 3, "question": "Go back where", "qsentId": 2}, {"answer": "I don't know. I should go back", "docId": "Martha-Marcy-May-Marlene.txt", "asentId": 5, "question": "I have to go, I can't stay gone", "qsentId": 4}, {"answer": "We like to entertain. Our friends come up for weekends and sometimes we have parties. It's just good to have space", "docId": "Martha-Marcy-May-Marlene.txt", "asentId": 7, "question": "Of course no one else lives here", "qsentId": 6}, {"answer": "I lost it", "docId": "Martha-Marcy-May-Marlene.txt", "asentId": 9, "question": "I got used to not having it", "qsentId": 8}, {"answer": " It looks good you little shit", "docId": "Martha-Marcy-May-Marlene.txt", "asentId": 11, "question": "You're making fun of me and I think it looks really good", "qsentId": 10}, {"answer": "It's no good", "docId": "Martha-Marcy-May-Marlene.txt", "asentId": 13, "question": "It's not dry", "qsentId": 12}, {"answer": "We had a garden where I lived", "docId": "Martha-Marcy-May-Marlene.txt", "asentId": 15, "question": "I'm good at some things", "qsentId": 14}, {"answer": "Did you know that guy", "docId": "Martha-Marcy-May-Marlene.txt", "asentId": 17, "question": "The guy in the store", "qsentId": 16}, {"answer": "I don't know, you tell me", "docId": "Martha-Marcy-May-Marlene.txt", "asentId": 19, "question": " He was staring at me like he knew me, did you talk to him about me", "qsentId": 18}, {"answer": "You want to hold him", "docId": "Martha-Marcy-May-Marlene.txt", "asentId": 21, "question": "Not if you don't want to. There are plenty of jobs to be done.  You'll find your role. It takes time for people to find their role in a new family", "qsentId": 20}, {"answer": "Sometimes I wonder if, maybe I could have taken better care of you", "docId": "Martha-Marcy-May-Marlene.txt", "asentId": 23, "question": "It does matter", "qsentId": 22}, {"answer": "No, my friend, I think the world of you, I'm just wondering if I should have come back and kept you in school and helped you go to college, you had so much potential", "docId": "Martha-Marcy-May-Marlene.txt", "asentId": 25, "question": "Teacher and a leader? What are you talking about? I always encouraged you to do more, but you shut me out", "qsentId": 24}, {"answer": "She's not", "docId": "Martha-Marcy-May-Marlene.txt", "asentId": 27, "question": "Who is this", "qsentId": 26}, {"answer": "Where is she", "docId": "Martha-Marcy-May-Marlene.txt", "asentId": 29, "question": "Who is this", "qsentId": 28}, {"answer": " What did you do? 56", "docId": "Martha-Marcy-May-Marlene.txt", "asentId": 31, "question": "One of them was sick, my friend knew which one it was", "qsentId": 30}, {"answer": "It feels like rules. They won't let me do anything. I can't even go on the house runs. I'd be great at taking shit", "docId": "Martha-Marcy-May-Marlene.txt", "asentId": 33, "question": "Sounds like it's about taking shit to me. 57", "qsentId": 32}, {"answer": "Are you accusing me of something? Because if you are, I'd like you to say it out loud so you can hear how absurd it sounds", "docId": "Martha-Marcy-May-Marlene.txt", "asentId": 35, "question": "You ask me to make more of an effort. I try to do that and you get upset. I can't win", "qsentId": 34}, {"answer": "Calm down, if you calm down no one will get hurt", "docId": "Martha-Marcy-May-Marlene.txt", "asentId": 37, "question": "We're not stealing, we don't want anything", "qsentId": 36}, {"answer": "Thanks mom. I'm sorry I ruined the party", "docId": "Martha-Marcy-May-Marlene.txt", "asentId": 39, "question": "Is it over", "qsentId": 38}, {"answer": "I'm fine", "docId": "Martha-Marcy-May-Marlene.txt", "asentId": 41, "question": "No. Do you", "qsentId": 40}, {"answer": "I know", "docId": "Martha-Marcy-May-Marlene.txt", "asentId": 43, "question": "Places", "qsentId": 42}, {"answer": "Haven't you learned anything", "docId": "Martha-Marcy-May-Marlene.txt", "asentId": 45, "question": "I felt like we had a connection", "qsentId": 44}, {"answer": "Are you going to send me away", "docId": "Martha-Marcy-May-Marlene.txt", "asentId": 47, "question": " Please don't. Please don't", "qsentId": 46}]